

Day of birth: 22/11/1993

Email: phanhuudinh@hotmail.com

Mobile: 0905221193

Address: 02 Cam Nam 9, Hoa Xuan, Da Nang

Facebook: fb.com/phanhuudinh

Career Profile

I have almost 2 years of web programming experience as a fullstack .NET developer with strong knowledge at both frontend backend. Also have more than 1 year as a game programmer, that very helpful for me to power up my skills about code performance and creation mindset.

Work Experience

Web Developer at IOT Link

November 2016 - Present

Web development bold client and server side for many insourcing project.

- Analytic, design and development web module
- Research and apply new technologies, techniques which useful and compatible with projects
- Development web api for mobile application
- Deployment and config environment for web server
- Support teamate.

.Net Developer at NAL Solution

August 2016 - November 2016

Development windows and web application for Japan Outsourcing project.

2D/3D Game programmer at Gameloft

June 2015 - August 2016

Java 2D game creation

- Implement game actor follow design
- Optimize performance for best quality and performance
- Support graphic-designer to use optimize tools.

C++/JAVA 3D Game publishing

- Implement anti hack/cheat for game
- Optimize and scale games for multy devices.

Projects

Xinkcity

2D/3D Maps platform which easy to integrate and development many applications around as an ecosystem. With this platform, we have many relative projects around.

Xickcity social network for business

Provide solution for business to create an website quickly and communication together. The website can be customized easy by many flexible module.

In this project, I developer web module follow SPA architecture with C# web api for backend and VueJs for frontend.

Xickcity Real Estate

The website make it easy for users to find information about real estate visually.

In this project, I responsible to config environment and build client side by use Webpack Reactjs and TypeScript. I also training and support teammate about those technology.

Lazo Application

An application Provide solution to manager seller

This application use SignalR for real time for tracking seller. In this project, I implement many functions on manager website and web api for mobile application.

N.O.V.A Legacy

Fantastic 3D game with more than 10 Million downloads on Play Store.

N.O.V.A Original

Awesome nostalgia 2D game which is the first Creation project of Gameloft's DAD studio.

Key Skills

C#
Javascript
ReactJs
TypeScript
HTML/CSS

MVC Web Api Git

SQL

1L/CSS Scrum

Other Skills

C/C++ Java Game development React Native NopCommerce Dotnetnuke

SVN IoT

VueJs

Education

HUE UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE

Grade: Good

Major: Informatics